<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>people on Light Roast Disco</title>
    <link>https://lightroastdisco.com/tags/people/</link>
    <description>Recent content in people on Light Roast Disco</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://lightroastdisco.com/tags/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Shipley</title>
      <link>https://lightroastdisco.com/people/matthew_shipley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lightroastdisco.com/people/matthew_shipley/</guid>
      <description>About Matthew Shipley was baptized by progressive house, but has since expanded to all genres of foot-moving fare. His live hardware sets are hypnotic with gradually evolving layers of crisp rhythms and futuristic synths. His DJ sets build momentum through mind-bending textures and heavy percussion, breaking open to memorable deep cut moments that make you bust out Shazam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nothing Gold</title>
      <link>https://lightroastdisco.com/people/nothinggold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lightroastdisco.com/people/nothinggold/</guid>
      <description>About Nothing Gold loves a mix of throwback disco funk and energetic old-school house that features modern jacking grooves blended into heavy warehouse stabs. His DJ sets often throw in fresh pop tracks and remixes of familair favorites. Devoted to bringing memorable moments, his sets are guaranteed to bring a fun vibe and create a safe place to express yourself on the dance floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Warden</title>
      <link>https://lightroastdisco.com/people/thewarden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lightroastdisco.com/people/thewarden/</guid>
      <description>About theWarden, a Chicago native, grew up hearing the sounds of bands like Depeche Mode and Nitzer Ebb which ignited his passion for electronic music from a young age. He was always drawn to the darker sounds of techno while still loving the levity of house music. theWarden tries to reconcile the dichotomy of these sounds in his mixes creating driving grooves with playful melodies and chord progressions that always keep is mixes fun and exciting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evn Gray</title>
      <link>https://lightroastdisco.com/people/evn_gray/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lightroastdisco.com/people/evn_gray/</guid>
      <description>About Evn Gray, coordinator of Light Roast Disco, brings colorful keyboards, pumping basslines, and lush disco melodies to his mixes. Primarily a percussionist, his music uses rhythm and relentless groove to intensify jazzy harmonies and guilty-pleasure acapellas. As a producer, he tries to distill and expand on specific elements to realize his own idea of different dancefloor sounds.
Inspirations Leon Vynehall, Kyle Hall, Tony Allen, Disclosure, Garrett David, Mike Dehnert, Derrick Carter, Jimmy Edgar</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
